KATE PRASOLEK

kate.prasolek@gmail.com | 07479929600 | London E1 4RS

kateprasolek.github.io/portfolio | behance.net/kateprasolek | linkedin.com/in/kateprasolek

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Reliable graphic designer with a friendly can-do attitude, experienced in both print and digital design. Self-learner of HTML, CSS and website design with good fundamentals of UI/UX best practices. Crafter with a natural eye for detail, layout and typography, currently learning motion design.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop	Adobe After Effects	HTML, CSS	Dotmailer / Dotdigital
Adobe inDesign	Adobe XD	Bootstrap	Litmus
Adobe Illustrator	PC and Mac	Wordpress CMS	Git / Github

INTERPERSONAL SOFT SKILLS

Attention to detail	Reliability	Time management	Can-do attitude
Creativity	Professionalism	Organisation skills	Ability to teamwork
Fast-learning	Enthusiasm	Prioritising	Communications skills

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Graphic Designer, London (Jan 2020 - present)

- Work on web UI/UX design and landing pages, create app concepts, wireframes, prototypes, mockups.
- Graphic design volunteer at Naturewatch Foundation creating digital and print assets.
- Manage small arts and crafts business, develop the brand identity, design banners and promotional materials. I achieved a 50% sales increase by consistent visuals and social media campaigns.

Graphic Designer at Wex Photo Video, London (Feb 2018 - Jan 2020)

- Create from brief to completion a wide range of marketing communications such as website banners, emails, gifs, brochures, leaflets, magazine's ads, large format prints and more.
- Work collaboratively with other teams and use feedback to produce final marketing creatives.
- Ensure compliance with brand guidelines and design consistency across all formats and channels.
- Manage multiple digital and print projects simultaneously adhering to meet deadlines.
- Supervise magazines' schedules, liaising with publishers and printers.
- Maintain templates and files, where I implemented a system that sped up the team's work-flow.

Freelance Graphic Designer, London (May 2016 - Feb 2018)

Create engaging websites, logos, banners, brochures, leaflets and marketing materials for various clients.

Receptionist and Research Bank Worker at Poplar Harca, London (May 2015 - Nov 2017)

Reception duties and data administration. I put into practice a structured data entry process, that was easier for volunteers to understand and lower the number of mistakes.

Master Team Member at Paul UK (Jun 2013 - Feb 2015)

Supervising shift, organising displays and stock, handling orders, sales plans distribution, reporting and customer service. I achieved a 5% increase in sales by visually managing displays throughout the day.

Saleswoman at Polkomtel SA (Oct 2010 - Dec 2012)

Phone customer service duties, selling and extending contracts.

Shift Supervisor at Pizzeria laPrimera (May 2009 - Sep 2010)

Organising shifts, stock and deliveries, reporting.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

EDUCATION AND TRAINING		
2020	Adobe CC After Effects and XD Experience Design, Google Web Designer, UI design.	
2018-19	Dotmailer/ Dotdigital, Adobe CC Illustrator.	
2017	Adobe Dreamweaver, HTML emails, HTML5/ CSS3, Javascript, jQuery.	
2016	Graphic Design, Layouts and Composition, Branding and Typography, Adobe Creative Suite Photoshop and inDesign.	
2008	Psychology, master degree, Silesian University.	